mondigroup.com 2016-12-01

# Mondi - Privacy

##  1\. General

Mondi Group respects your privacy. This policy outlines the type of information we may collect from our website and how we may use that information. We may update this policy from time to time, so please check it occasionally. By using this site and/or providing personal information, you agree to the terms of this policy.

##  2\. Collection and use of personal information

Personal information includes information such as your name, address, telephone number, date of birth and e-mail address. Generally, you may visit our website without providing us with any personal information. However, from time to time we may need to collect your personal information for a specific purpose, for example providing you with information that you have requested. If there are other purposes for which we will use your personal information, we will tell you at the time of collection. By providing this information, you consent to the use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes notified.

##  3\. Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information to our associated companies and to third parties for our own business, marketing and website-related purposes. We will not sell, transfer or disclose your personal information to third parties unless we have your express consent or if we need to do so to fulfil your request or for other related purposes and we will never sell, transfer or disclose your personal data to third parties for their marketing use.

##  4\. Cookies and other non-identifying information

We may automatically collect some non-personal information when you visit our website. Examples include the type of Internet browser used, the type of computer operating system used, the connection speed used and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site. We may also store some information on your computer, in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. We may use this to collect other information during your visit to our websites, such as the particular site areas you visit and the activities in which you participate at our web sites. Most Internet browsers allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You can obtain information about how to manage cookies at: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). We may use this information to tailor our websites to better match your interests and preferences and to improve our products, services and marketing programmes.

##  5\. Security and accuracy

The accuracy and security of your personal data is important to us and we have put in place physical and electronic procedures to maintain the security of your personal information. Only authorised administrative staff will have access to that information. If you have submitted personal information to us and would like that information deleted from our records, or updated, please email us on [info@mondigroup.com](mailto:info@mondigroup.com). Please allow us time to update your records.

On some pages of our website you have the option to subscribe to newsletters, feeds, etc. Such subscriptions might require you to provide your email address, as well as other information that help us provide the requested service. Users who wish to no longer receive our newsletter or promotional emails may click on a link named “ _unsubscribe_ ” which is embedded in the email sent by Mondi. Feeds can be unsubscribed by deleting the feed from your RSS reader.

##  6\. Transfers

Any personal information we collect will be stored in the country in which it is collected and may also be transferred to the UK. Personal information collected within the European Union (“EU”) will not be transferred outside the EU without your consent.

##  7\. Contact Us

If you have any further questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us.

|  Mondi plc  
---  
Building 1, 1st Floor  
Aviator Park, Station Road  
UK - KT15 2PG, Addlestone Surrey  
Tel: +44 (0)1932 826 300  
Fax: +44 (0)1932 826 350  
» Google Maps  
|  Mondi Limited  
---  
4th Floor, No.3 Melrose Boulevard  
Melrose Arch, 2196, Gauteng,  
Republic of South Africa  
Tel: + 27 (0)11 994 5400  
Fax: +27 (0)11 520 4688  
» Google Maps  
  
Last change: 22/10/2013
